<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ajilenakh</title><link>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/</link><description>Recent content on Ajilenakh</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automating Java Web Application Deployment with CI/CD and Spring Boot</title><link>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/posts/cicdautomation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/posts/cicdautomation/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This project involves setting up a &lt;strong>Spring Boot application&lt;/strong> to automate the &lt;strong>CI/CD pipeline&lt;/strong> for deploying a Java web application. The goal is to simplify the development, deployment, and management process by integrating version control, automated builds, testing, and deployments, while leveraging modern DevOps practices. This approach eliminates the need for complex server setups by packaging everything into a self-contained &lt;strong>JAR file&lt;/strong>, including the &lt;strong>embedded Tomcat&lt;/strong> server, and using automated deployment workflows.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DBM Air</title><link>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/projects/dbm-air/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/projects/dbm-air/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="dbm-air-your-flight-booking-companion">DBM Air: Your Flight Booking Companion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>DBM Air began as a college assignment, but it quickly turned into a collaborative project fueled by curiosity and a desire to learn. My friend and I set out to build a functional flight booking website, which became our first real step into web development.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="about-the-project">About the Project&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The website is designed to simplify the flight booking experience. Although we were new to coding, this project became a hands-on opportunity to apply and expand our knowledge. We created:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>TubeCrate</title><link>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/projects/tubecrate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ajilenakh.vercel.app/projects/tubecrate/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="tubecrate-simplifying-video-downloads">TubeCrate: Simplifying Video Downloads&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>TubeCrate was born out of necessity. Finding a reliable website to download HD videos with audio in .mp4 format can be surprisingly difficult. This project aims to solve that problem by creating a streamlined solution for downloading videos efficiently and conveniently.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="about-the-project">About the Project&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>TubeCrate focuses on providing a user-friendly API for downloading videos with high-quality audio. While the backend functionality is robust, the frontend is still in progress—a task that, admittedly, feels less exciting but remains essential for a complete user experience.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>