<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ajilenakh</title><link>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/</link><description>Recent content on Ajilenakh</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tomcat Server: Building and Deploying Java Web Applications</title><link>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/posts/tomcat-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/posts/tomcat-server/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This project involves setting up a &lt;strong>Tomcat server&lt;/strong> for hosting and deploying a simple Java web application. The server has been installed and configured on my local machine, following this &lt;a href="https://www.atlantic.net/dedicated-server-hosting/how-to-install-tomcat-on-arch-linux/">comprehensive guide&lt;/a>. The goal is to create a robust pipeline for developing, deploying, and managing Java web applications with automation and multiple environment support.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="current-status">Current Status&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The Tomcat server is up and running on my local machine. Next steps involve creating and deploying a Java web application while planning for scalability and testing in different environments.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DBM Air</title><link>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/projects/dbm-air/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/projects/dbm-air/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="dbm-air-your-flight-booking-companion">DBM Air: Your Flight Booking Companion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>DBM Air began as a college assignment, but it quickly turned into a collaborative project fueled by curiosity and a desire to learn. My friend and I set out to build a functional flight booking website, which became our first real step into web development.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="about-the-project">About the Project&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The website is designed to simplify the flight booking experience. Although we were new to coding, this project became a hands-on opportunity to apply and expand our knowledge. We created:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>TubeCrate</title><link>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/projects/tubecrate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog-git-development-ajilenakhs-projects.vercel.app/projects/tubecrate/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="tubecrate-simplifying-video-downloads">TubeCrate: Simplifying Video Downloads&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>TubeCrate was born out of necessity. Finding a reliable website to download HD videos with audio in .mp4 format can be surprisingly difficult. This project aims to solve that problem by creating a streamlined solution for downloading videos efficiently and conveniently.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="about-the-project">About the Project&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>TubeCrate focuses on providing a user-friendly API for downloading videos with high-quality audio. While the backend functionality is robust, the frontend is still in progress—a task that, admittedly, feels less exciting but remains essential for a complete user experience.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>